Hello, everyone.
To all the friends
following Entertainment Star.
I am your host,
Li Siyu.
Today, the musicians
we have invited for you
are The Landlord's Cat.
Welcome, both of you.
I can already see here
that there are many...
Messages from our listeners
are already coming in.
Everyone is discussing
the recent hit drama 'The Legend of Huayue'
and its trending memes.
Zhou Zhi.
Unfortunately, after it aired,
his acting skills faced
widespread criticism.
Especially some of
the acting clips.
It also became popular material
for netizens' fan creations.
About season two of "The Legend of Huayue",
is there any news?
They've confirmed that for season two,
they are changing the male lead.
Morning, Sister Hu.
Where is Jinxi? Why isn't he with you?
He told me early this morning
that he was coming to see you.
[Rooftop]
[No throwing objects from height]
Jin Xi, Jin Xi, Jin Xi!
Come down.
Bro!
Come down, come down.
Don't come any closer!
Bro, if you do something stupid,
I'll do something stupid too!
Let me ask you.
When you got
the script,
didn't everyone in the company say
the screenwriter wrote it well?
Yes, yes, yes.
When you all saw
the trailer,
didn't you say the visuals were
beautiful?
Beautiful, very beautiful.
When I wrapped up,
didn't the director praise me
for being so dedicated?
Then everyone clapped for me.
They clapped.
You are our pride,
Jinxi.
Let me ask you.
When we wrapped up,
didn't the director
seriously praise me?
The whole crew clapped for me.
Right, right, right.
Jinxi, come down quickly.
You are our pride.
Please.
Brother.
Step back.
Okay.
We won't move.
Sister Hu, Eason.
Now everyone in the world
is laughing at me.
No, no.
I can't take it anymore.
No, bro.
I'm so grateful
for the time I've worked with you all.
I'm too ashamed to face everyone.
Jinxi!
Bro, don't! Bro!
Farewell.
Jinxi!
Bro! Jinxi!
Did I scare you?
Bro,
are you kidding?
My acting was convincing, right?
You couldn't tell, could you?
You couldn't tell. You couldn't tell.
I fooled you, didn't I?
Who says using eye drops
means you can't act?
I used eye drops.
Could you tell?
Amazing.
We were all won
over by your acting.
Amazing.
Great.
Jinxi, you're awesome.
So,
you were completely unaffected
by those bad comments, right?
I was completely unaffected.
I knew it.
How could our Jinxi be defeated
by such a small matter?
Next, take a good trip
and relax.
Yeah.
And think about
your second album.
Hold off on the album for now.
I need some new inspiration.
Did you guys hear that The Legend of Huayue
is getting a second season?
Contact Director Zha.
I plan to continue playing
the role of Murong Fengshan.
This time,
I will throw myself into
the role even more.
I want to
burn myself out.
Okay.
Alright,
I'll contact the director as soon as possible.
So,
are you really okay?
More than okay.
I'm so fired up right now
that it's overflowing.
Just one or two trolls,
no need to care.
Let's go.
Bro,
your acting skills,
your perspective,
I
admire it.
Isn't the lead for season two of The Legend of Huayue
going to be replaced?
And the other shows that reached out to us...
He can't know about this.
In his current state,
we still can't tell him.
However,
I already have
a compromise in mind.
I suggest Jin Xi's crying scenes
be declared as an intangible cultural heritage.
Record of early humans failing to tame facial muscles.
I'm so triggered.
Xi's fans are here for damage control.
Your idol's fight scenes
are like slow-motion replays.
Do you
know
what it means to
be full of emotion?
You must be Jin Xi's burner account.
Every time you gaze affectionately at the female lead,
it looks like a blind masseur searching for acupoints.
Latest inside news:
Jin Xi did 433 retakes in Huayue Tale,
breaking the national production record!
Anyway, everyone has reached a consensus,
which is that Jin Xi's kissing scenes are terrible.
Right?
Oh my, I can't even imagine
being kissed like that by a guy.
How bad would it feel?
Victor Bastidas rocks the stage.
Sounds great.
You sang beautifully.
Thank you. Thank you for sharing, Mochou.
Next, our band
will continue to perform for you.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You didn't even bring your assistant.
Did you sneak out again?
When are you going to
release your next album?
I'm waiting to hear it.
No rush.
I plan to continue acting in the second half of the year.
What's with that look?
Look?
I don't have any look.
Did you watch my
Legend of Huayue?
I
watched a few clips.
Let me tell you,
you must have watched the videos
edited by my haters.
You have to watch Legend of Huayue
from beginning to end
to understand it.
Come on, Jinxi.
Don't compete with me on haters.
In this regard,
I have much more experience than you.
True.
Look at me,
I don't even think about acting.
It's too tiring.
No,
I think I'm good at
both music and acting.
You see, I've already won a Golden Melody Award.
My next goal
is to win a Golden Acting Award.
Well, sister,
I wish you success.
Thank you.
I have a schedule tomorrow,
so I'll get going.
Bye.
What are you doing?
Sorry.
Sounds good.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong?
Don't you think
we should get to know each other?
Why?
Because just now, didn't you...
What did I do?
I...
Didn't we just kiss?
Kiss?
I think what you did was wrong.
How is it wrong?
You should have at least
asked for my permission.
But you didn't dodge.
I...
See?
You didn't want to dodge, right?
Good night.
Thank you.
No.
Jin Xi.
Are you listening to me?
I'm listening.
So what do you think?
Can you say it again?
Where did you stop listening?
The beginning.
It's like this.
As for 'The Legend of Hua Yue',
they don't plan to shoot a second season.
But there's good news.
Caomang Music Festival
- I'm not going.
- invited us.
Why?
Sister, do you know the wooden barrel effect?
What?
The wooden barrel effect.
It means
the amount of water
a wooden barrel can hold
depends on
the length of its shortest board.
For example,
the length of my music board
is here.
Then people's evaluation of my performance
is right here.
Okay.
Do you know about this?
I know.
I am that barrel.
I understand.
So from now on,
I just want to prove my acting skills.
Everything related to music,
stop it all.
No negotiation?
No negotiation, Sister.
I'm waiting for your script.
Duo queue, come on.
Wait.
Get up,
get up quickly.
Actually,
there is another script that's not bad.
A leading male role in a costume drama.
That's great,
take it.
But it's not a TV series,
it's a musical.
'A Chinese Ghost Story'.
'A Chinese Ghost Story'?
Isn't that the story
of Nie Xiaoqian and Ning Caichen?
I've seen that movie.
Sister Hu, you are awesome!
Alright.
Put me down quickly.
You sit down first,
we still have details
that need to be confirmed.
The person in charge there,
is definitely fine.
But,
their troupe has a core figure.
That is their troupe's
exclusive director named Ning Jin.
Director?
This person is known for being strict
and has very high requirements for actors.
No matter who it is,
she treats everyone equally.
But you don't need to worry too much.
Tonight,
they happen to be reviving a
previously
very popular musical.
I got three tickets.
The three of us will go together.
After the musical,
I'll arrange for the producer,
the person in charge and the director
to have a meal with us.
Leave your matters to me.
I will definitely get it sorted out for you.
How is it?
You think the musical is interesting, right?
It's really nice.
Sounds good, looks good.
Bravo!
Thank you.
Thank you, everyone.
I am the producer of this musical,
Wu Qiming.
Please allow me to introduce
all of today's
creative team members.
The actress of the Peach Blossom Fairy,
Liang Jing.
Great!
Beautiful!
So beautiful!
Great!
The actor of the male lead, Zhongli,
Du Heying.
So handsome!
The female lead,
the actress of Yiren,
Bai Feixin.
Absolutely beautiful!
Next,
is the interactive session
of our Xiyin Theater Troupe.
We will invite
a lucky audience member
to ask a question.
Our famous director,
Ning Jin,
will answer this question for you.
Who will be today's
lucky audience member?
Me! Me!
Over here!
Me!
Ask me!
Here! Here!
So many people are raising their hands.
Alright.
This luck belongs to you.
Thank you for the wonderful performance.
But here,
I want to take this time before
the theater dismisses
to thank a person
who is very important
to us.
Jin Xi,
do you still remember?
Today is the release day
of your third single,
"July 24th."
We will always support you
and never leave you.
Jin Xi, Jin Xi, we'll never leave you!
Jin Xi, Jin Xi, we'll always love you!
What's going on?
Jin Xi,
where are you?
Let us see you, please.
Look! Look over there!
I'll cover the rear.
Go quickly.
Jin Xi, go!
Don't make this hard for me.
Stay safe, you guys.
Stay safe.
Got it, sis.
Understood, sis.
Sister Hu said the scene is a bit chaotic,
so we don't need to go.
Okay.
She just needs to have dinner with the director tonight.
The musical was so interesting.
I'm glad you liked it, bro.
Let's go home now then.
No.
I want to go somewhere.
You sneaked out yesterday
and came here, didn't you?
Don't tell Sister Hu.
Don't worry, I'm always on your side.
Bro, what are you waiting for?
Sister Hu.
How was the dinner last night?
It went well.
It couldn't have gone better.
So does that mean
I can play Ning Caichen?
Sister Hu, this pause of yours
is making me very nervous.
The director said during dinner
that he hopes to see you in person
and wants you to join
the audition for the lead actor of A Chinese Ghost Story.
The director wants to audition me?
Find all the movies
and TV series video materials
of 'A Chinese Ghost Story' for me.
I need them for reference.
Right away.
So,
you are willing to go.
The fact that the director wants to interview me
just proves
how responsible they are.
Plus, it should be
a mutual effort for both of us.
I will put in
100% effort.
I will definitely become
the Ning Caichen in her heart.
Jin Xi.
You are amazing.
In my heart, you are
the most perfect Ning Caichen.
I didn't make the wrong choice.
Thank you, Director.
Ning Caichen.
Sister Hu,
so many people are here to audition for Ning Caichen.
We're just going through the motions.
Look at all these people.
Who looks more like Ning Caichen than you?
Are you Mr. Du Heying?
Yes.
Hello.
It's an honor to audition with you.
Um, sir,
could we get your autograph?
Of course.
Sign here.
Okay.
Here you go.
Thank you, sir.
Sir,
you've worked with Director Ning on so many plays.
The role of Ning Caichen
is definitely yours.
Yes.
You and Director Ning,
in our musical theatre circle,
are the most classic duo.
Right.
Not at all.
Director Ning's rules,
you all know.
No matter what role it is,
it all depends on the final
audition results.
Alright, good luck.
Okay.
Look at Mr. Du Heying's stage presence,
his style.
So handsome.
Hello, Director. Hello, everyone.
I've been in the musical industry for eight years
and sung countless songs.
But the one that moves me the most
and my favorite
is Director Ning's work,
"Summer Flower" from "Jianjia".
Today,
I want to try singing a cappella
for you all.
The director looks quite strict.
I'm a little nervous.
Okay.
What are you nervous about?
You will be fine.
Just perform normally.
Sister Hu is right.
So impressive.
Great.
Hu,
didn't you say they
were just going through the motions?
Seeing you here,
everyone feels a sense of crisis.
Don't worry.
Is that so?
Next, Jin Xi.
Jin Xi.
You'll be fine.
Absolutely.
I can't wait.
Good luck.
He has a lot of fans.
You don't even know Jinxi?
I don't know.